

About

Currently open for new opportunities as UX Designer, UX/UI Designer I am an enthusiastic and dedicated professional with a solid academic background in Human-Computer Interaction and Design, Research and Computer Science. I am passionate by user experience design, user interface design, user research, web development and new technologies.

Core expertise

- · Design Thinking workshops
- User Research
- User Testing
- Prototyping
- · Design Systems

Tools

- · Adobe Suite
- Figma
- FigJam
- Miro

Soft skills

- Communication
- Flexibility
- · Time management
- · Problem-solving mindset
- · Team spirit
- Positivity

Languages

English (Bilingual)
French (Proficient)
Arabic (Native)
Spanish (Notions)
Hungarian (Notions)

Yassine Ben Lakhdhar

UX/UI designer 🦄

Portfolio LinkedIn

(+33) 6 27 49 25 49 yblakhdhar@gmail.com Paris 75013

Immediately available Geographic mobility

Work experience

12/2021 to 12/2022 (Paris, France)

User Experience Designer, Ubisoft Entertainment

In this world-leading video game company, I have as a UX Designer at the Online Services division:

- Actively collaborated within a team of 15 UX and UI designers applying best practices in user experience design and on the application of a Design System to online services applications;
- Assisted the maintenance of the game statistics application in the Ubisoft Connect platform, exposing specific and engaging stats per game for more than 150 million players online on Mobile, PC and Console;
- Proposed an improved user experience on how Ubisoft Store reduction coupons are granted internally at Ubisoft, impacting +20K collaborators worldwide along with a UI designer, and Project Manager;
- Performed user interviews, user tests, and prototype of a User Account linking solution,
 successfully converting over 2 million players to claim Ubisoft in-game rewards and fresh content on all their gaming platforms using their Amazon Prime subscriptions.

03/2021 - 08/2021 (Paris, France)

Interaction & Experience Design Research Intern, <u>EX(SITU team - LISN research lab - INRIA Saclay</u>

As a researcher at ex)situ research lab, I was able to explore human-computer interaction and interaction design research, specifically how dance practitioners document their work:

 Collaborated alongside a choreographer and design researcher, designed and developed an interactive web-based mobile-first application used by several dancers and choreographers in Paris.

09/2019 - 01/2020 (Debrecen, Hungary)

Customer Support Agent, Ryanair

In this company that is Europe's largest airline, I have had the following experience:

Treatment of customers needs and requests over calls and live chat, which helped my
understanding on the importance of keeping track and measure customer success and
customer churn at the customer support level at the online division to propose the best solutions.

Education

12/2021 - 10/2022 (Paris, France)

Web Design, Ecole Webstart

09/2020 - 09/2021 (Paris, France)

Computer Science MSc, Institut Polytechnique de Paris

09/2016 - 06/2020 (Debrecen, Hungary)

Computer Science BSc, University of Debrecen

09/2014 - 06/2016 (Cambridge, UK)

Cambridge A levels, Cambridge International

Certificates

- Development (Modern JavaScript, HTML & CSS Udemy Certification)
- Digital Marketing (Google Digital Garage Certification)
- Agile Methodology (Virtual Agile Teams -IIL, Inc.)

Personal interests

- Football (Debrecen Gladiators American football team player - 11/2018 to 08/2020)
- Event organization (Debrecen University International Student Union Member -10/2018 to 10/2019)
- Music (beat production and rapping)